A Guide to the Island Resources Foundation records FA1200
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects and Occasional Papers, 1894-1895, 1946, 1956, 1961-1964, 1968-2016; 3; 33.3 Cubic Feet 85 letter document boxes, 1 half-letter document box, and 1 flat file folder
  - #108, St. Kitts, South East Peninsula, Land Use Management Plan, Correspondence with St. Kitts Government, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 994)
  - #108, St. Kitts, South East Peninsula, Land Use Management Plan, Correspondence with US Agency for International Development, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 995)
  - #108, St. Kitts, South East Peninsula, Land Use Management Plan, Public Management and Policy Planning Project, Robert Nathan Associates, 1985-1986 (Box 94, Folder 996)
  - #108, St. Kitts, South East Peninsula, Land Use Management Plan, Report, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 997-998)
  - #108, St. Kitts, South East Peninsula, Land Use Management Plan, Report, Bruce Potter Photographs and Negatives, 1986 March (Box 191, Folder 2204-2205)
  - #108, St. Kitts, South East Peninsula, Land Use Management Plan, Report, S. Goodwin Photographs, 1985 October (Box 191, Folder 2206)
  - #108, St. Kitts, South East Peninsula, Land Use Management Plan, Report, Photographs, 1986 (Box 191, Folder 2207)
  - #109, CAMPNET (Coastal Area Management and Planning Network), Proposals, Contracts, and Other External Correspondence, 1986-1987, 1989-1990 (Box 94, Folder 999)
  - #109, CAMPNET (Coastal Area Management and Planning Network), Internal Correspondence with John Clark, 1986-1989 (Box 94, Folder 1000)
  - #109, CAMPNET (Coastal Area Management and Planning Network), Newsletters, 1986-1991 (Box 94, Folder 1001)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, Forms, 1986, 1988-1990 (Box 94, Folder 1002)
  - #110, East Caribbean NGOs, Mini Grant Awards, 1987-1989, 1991-1995 (Box 95, Folder 1003)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, Correspondence with Cooperation TA Organizations, 1986-1989 (Box 95, Folder 1004)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, Goldman Foundation, 1994 (Box 95, Folder 1005)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, National Trust of Historic Preservation Workshop, 1991, 1994 (Box 95, Folder 1006)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, Helmut K. Anheier, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 1007)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, Internal Documents, Memorandum, etc., 1986-1990 (Box 95, Folder 1008)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, General Correspondence, 1986-1990, 1995 (Box 95, Folder 1009)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, Correspondence with US Agency for International Development, 1986-1987 (Box 95, Folder 1010)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, NGOs, Final Reports to World Wildlife Foundation (WWF)/Rockefeller Brothers Fund (RBF), 1991 (Box 95, Folder 1011)
  - #110, East Caribbean NGOs, End of the Year One and Two Reports, 1987, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 1012)
  - #110, East Caribbean NGOs, Survey Report, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 1013)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, NGOs, Interim Report to Funders, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 1014)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, Correspondence with World Wildlife Foundation (WWF), 1986-1991, 1994 (Box 95, Folder 1015)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, Correspondence and Report with Rockefeller Brothers Fund (RBF), 1987-1992 (Box 95, Folder 1016)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, Rockefeller Brothers Fund (RBF) Proposal and Work Plan, Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 95, Folder 1017)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, Grant Award, World Wildlife Foundation (WWF) Correspondence, 1986-1992 (Box 96, Folder 1018)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, Proposal, World Wildlife Foundation (WWF), 1986 (Box 96, Folder 1019)
  - #110, East Caribbean NGOs, Newsletters and Bulletins, 1987-1994 (Box 96, Folder 1020)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, NGOs, Directory, 1995 (Box 96, Folder 1021)
  - #110, East Caribbean NGOs, Donor Directory Republication, 1987, 1994-1995 (Box 96, Folder 1022)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, NGOs, Directory, 1991 (Box 96, Folder 1023)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, NGOs, Mukti Fund, 1991-2004 (Box 96, Folder 1024-1025)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, Organizational Profiles, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 1026)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, NGO Project Hand-Out, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 1027)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, World Wildlife Foundation (WWF), Rockefeller Brothers Fund (RBF), Island Resources Foundation Project Announcement, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 1028)
  - #110, East Caribbean Institutional Development, NGO Project Database, 1987, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 1029)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, Agreement, Correspondence with the Community Foundation of the Virgin Islands, 2014-2015 (Box 97, Folder 1030)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, Correspondence with Laurance S. Rockefeller, etc., 1987, 1994, 2002-2003, 2012 (Box 97, Folder 1031)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 1988 Nominations, 1987-1988 (Box 97, Folder 1032)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 1989 Nominations (Box 97, Folder 1033)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 1990 Nominations (Box 97, Folder 1034)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 1991 Nominations (Box 97, Folder 1035)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 1993 Award (Box 97, Folder 1036)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 1995 Award, 1993-1995 (Box 97, Folder 1037)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 1996 Nominations (Box 97, Folder 1038)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 1997 Nominations (Box 97, Folder 1039)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 1998 Nominations, 1994-1995, 1997-1998 (Box 97, Folder 1040)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 1999 Nominations and Award, 1998-1999 (Box 97, Folder 1041)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 2000 Nominations and Award, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 1042)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 2001 Nominations and Award (Box 97, Folder 1043)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 2002 Nominations and Award, 1989-1992, 1994-2002 (Box 97, Frame 1044)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 2003 Nominations and Award, 2000-2003 (Box 97, Folder 1045)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 2004 Nominations and Award (Box 97, Folder 1046)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 2005 Nominations and Award, 2005-2006, 2012 (Box 98, Folder 1047)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 2006 Nominations and Award, 2006-2007 (Box 98, Folder 1048)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 2007 Nominations and Award, 2008 (Box 98, Folder 1049)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 2008-2009 Nominations and Award, 2009-2010 (Box 98, Folder 1050)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 2010 Nominations and Award, 2010-2011 (Box 98, Folder 1051)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 2011 Nominations and Award, 2005-2012 (Box 98, Folder 1052)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 2013 Nominations and Award (Box 98, Folder 1053)
  - #111, Euan P. McFarlane Environmental Award, 2014 Nominations and Award, 2011, 2013-2014 (Box 98, Folder 1054)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Project Announcement, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 1055)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Statement of Work Documentation, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 1056)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Personnel, Internal, 1987-1990 (Box 98, Folder 1057)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Printing, 1990-1991 (Box 98, Folder 1058)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Distribution of Published Reports, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 1059)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Responses to Published Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 99, Folder 1060)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Synthesis Publications Request, Distribution List, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 1061)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1986-1988, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 1062)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Quarterly Progress Reports to US Agency to International Development, 1987-1990 (Box 99, Folder 1063)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), and Correspondence with the US Agency for International Development (IRF Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA)), 1986-1991 (Box 99, Folder 1064)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Correspondence with Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA) (IRF and US Agency for International Development), 1987-1991, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 1065)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), US Agency for International Development Memorandum of Agreement with Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA), 1986-1987, 1989, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 1066)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Memorandum of Agreement with Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA), 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 1067)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Memorandum of Understanding Document File, 1987 (Box 99, Folder 1068)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Synthesis, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 1069)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Correspondence with Nevis Country Environmental Profile, 1987, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 1070)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Antigua Profile, 1989-1992 (Box 99, Folder 1071)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Dominica Profile, 1989-1991 (Box 99, Folder 1072)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Grenada, 1988-1991 (Box 99, Folder 1073)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Grenada, 1988-1991 (Box 100, Folder 1074)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), St. Kitts/Nevis Profile, 1989-1991 (Box 100, Folder 1075)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), St. Lucia National Committee, etc., 1987-1992 (Box 100, Folder 1076-1977)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), St. Vincent Profile, 1989-1991 (Box 100, Folder 1078)
  - #112, Eastern Caribbean Country Environmental Profile (CEP), Environmental Agenda for the 1990s, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 1079)
  - #113, St. Croix Marine Archaeological Survey, Proposal, 1983, 1987-1988 (Box 100, Folder 1080)
  - #113, St. Croix Marine Archaeological Survey, Contract and Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 100, Folder 1081)
  - #113, St. Croix Marine Archaeological Survey, Correspondence withe Virgin Islands Government, 1987-1989 (Box 100, Folder 1082)
  - #113, St. Croix Marine Archaeological Survey, Personnel, 1987-1988 (Box 100, Folder 1083)
  - #113, St. Croix Marine Archaeological Survey, Correspondence with EG&G, 1988-1989 (Box 100, Folder 1084)
  - #113, St. Croix Marine Archaeological Survey, Limetree Bay, Report, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 1085)
  - #113, St. Croix Marine Archaeological Survey, Limetree Bay, Report, Photographs, 1989 (Box 191, Folder 2208)
  - #113, St. Croix Marine Archaeological Survey, Schooner Channel, Report, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 1086)
  - #114, St. Croix Water Quality, Plan, Proposal, and Contract, 1987, 1989-1991 (Box 101, Folder 1087)
  - #114, St. Croix Water Quality, Internal, Personnel, 1987, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 1088)
  - #114, St. Croix Water Quality, Port Authority Correspondence and Reports, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 101, Folder 1089)
  - #114, St. Croix Water Quality, Third Port, Progress Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 101, Folder 1090)
  - #114, St. Croix Water Quality, Third Port, Progress Reports, Photographs, 1989-1990 (Box 192, Folder 2209-2213)
  - #115, Montserrat, Organization of Eastern Caribbean States, Contract Documents, Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 101, Folder 1091)
  - #115, Montserrat, Organization of Eastern Caribbean States, Internal Documents, 1987-1988 (Box 101, Folder 1092)
  - #115, Montserrat, Organization of Eastern Caribbean States, Land Resource Study (Box 101, Folder 1093)
  - #116, Red Point, St. Thomas, Proposal, Contract, Correspondence with Maguire Group, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 1094)
  - #116, Red Point, St. Thomas, Internal. Personnel, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 1095)
  - #116, Red Point, St. Thomas, Reports, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 1096)
  - #117, Seagrass Study, Proposal, Contract, Port Authority Correspondence, 1987, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 1097)
  - #117, Seagrass Study, Other Correspondence, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 1098)
  - #117, Seagrass Study, Internal Documents, Personnel, 1987, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 1099)
  - #117, Seagrass Study, Final Report, 1st-4th Quarters, 1987-1988 (Box 101, Folder 1100)
  - #117, Seagrass Study, Seagrass Transplantation, Phase I Report, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 1101)
  - #117, Seagrass Study, Seagrass Transplantation, Final Report, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 1102)
  - #118, Virgin Islands Land Use Survey, Proposal, 1988-1989 (Box 102, Folder 1103)
  - #118, Virgin Islands Land Use Survey, Contract, 1989 (Box 102, Folder 1104)
  - #118, Virgin Islands Land Use Survey, Internal, Personnel, 1988-1989 (Box 102, Folder 1105)
  - #118, Virgin Islands Land Use Survey, Legend Description, 1989 (Box 102, Folder 1106)
  - #118, Virgin Islands Land Use Survey, Potter "Course" Product (Box 102, Folder 1107)
  - #118, Virgin Islands Land Use Survey, Correspondence with the Virgin Islands Government, 1988-1989 (Box 102, Folder 1108)
  - #118, Virgin Islands Land Use Survey, Reports, 1981, 1989 (Box 102, Folder 1109)
  - #118, Virgin Islands Land Use Survey, Final Report, 1989 (Box 102, Folder 1110-1111)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Proposal, 1988-1989 (Box 102, Folder 1112)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Grant Negotiations and Grant Award, 1989-1991, 1993-1995 (Box 102, Folder 1113)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Proposal Writing Workshop, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 1114)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Proposal Writing Overview, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 1115)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Internships, 1990-1995 (Box 103, Folder 1116)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Internal Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 103, Folder 1117-1118)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Correspondence, 1989-1992, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 1119)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box 103, Folder 1120)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Correspondence with Caribbean Conservation Association (CCA), 1990, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 1121)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Correspondence with ENCORE, 1993-1995 (Box 103, Folder 1122)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Correspondence with US Agency for International Development, 1989-1996 (Box 103, Folder 1123)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Jessie Smith Noyes Foundation, 1986, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 1124)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Homeland Foundation Proposal, 1990-1993 (Box 104, Folder 1125)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1991-1992, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1126)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Biodiversity Support Program/World Wildlife Foundation (WWF) Biodiversity Program, Proposal and Grant Award Documents, 1990-1995 (Box 104, Folder 1127)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, World Wildlife Foundation (WWF) Biodiversity Project, Correspondence and Reports, 1992-1996 (Box 104, Folder 1128)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Proposal to Compton Foundation, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 1129)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Proposal to Weeden Foundation, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1130)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Charles Stewart Mott Foundation Proposal, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 1131)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Avian Biodiversity Proposal, 1993-1994 (Box 104, Folder 1132)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Pew Charitable Trusts Proposal, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 1133)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, NGO Environment Information Centers, 1993-1995 (Box 104, Folder 1134)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Country Information Forms, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 1135)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Reports to US Agency for International Development, 1990-1995 (Box 104, Folder 1136-1137)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Mid-Term Evaluation, 1991-1992 (Box 105, Folder 1138)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 105, Folder 1139)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Board Members Workshop for NGOs, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 1140)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Publication, Widening the Circle of Leadership, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 1141)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Fiscal Management Manual, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 1142)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Planning Guide for Preparing an Institutional Development Plan, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 1143)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Fundraising Workshop, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 1144)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, Strengthening NGO Information Base, 1993 (Box 105, Folder 1145)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, NGO Program Handout (Box 105, Folder 1146)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, NGO Program Resources, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 1147)
  - #120, US Agency for International Development (USAID)-Private Voluntary Organization (PVO) Matching Fund Grant, NGO Program Fundraising, 1992-1994 (Box 105, Folder 1148)
  - #122, Virgin Islands Resource Management Cooperative (VIRMC) Planning Grant, Proposal, Grant Award, MacArthur Correspondence, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 1149)
  - #123, Post Hurricane Hugo, Department of Planning and Natural Resources, Proposal, 1988, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 1150)
  - #123, Post Hurricane Hugo, Department of Planning and Natural Resources, Contract, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 1151)
  - #123, Post Hurricane Hugo, Department of Planning and Natural Resources, Internal Correspondence and Personnel Matters, 1980, 1987-1990 (Box 105, Folder 1151)
  - #123, Post Hurricane Hugo, Department of Planning and Natural Resources, Other Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 105, Folder 1152)
  - #123, Post Hurricane Hugo, Department of Planning and Natural Resources, Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 106, Folder 1153)
  - #123, Post Hurricane Hugo, Department of Planning and Natural Resources, Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 106, Folder 1154)
  - #124, Buck Island Reef Assessment, Proposal and Contract, 1990-1992 (Box 106, Folder 1155)
  - #124, Buck Island Reef Assessment, Personnel, 1990-1991 (Box 106, Folder 1156)
  - #124, Buck Island Reef Assessment, Final Report, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 1157)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Contract, 1991-1992 (Box 106, Folder 1158)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Department of Planning and Natural Resources (DPNR) Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 106, Folder 1159)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Internal Correspondence and Personnel Matters, 1991-1992 (Box 106, Folder 1160)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Other Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 106, Folder 1161)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Clippings and Miscellaneous Infomation, 1991, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 1162)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, University of the Virgin Islands, 1991-1993 (Box 106, Folder 1163)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Botany Bay Area of Particular Concern, Area of Preservation and Restoration Report, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 1164)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Magens Bay Area of Particular Concern Report, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 1165)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Mandahl Bay, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 1166)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Mangrove Bay, Benner Bay, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 1167)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, St. Thomas Harbor and Waterfront Area of Particular Concern, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 1168)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Vessup Bay, Red Hook Area of Particular Concern report, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 1169)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Chocolate Hole, Great Cruz Bay, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 1170)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Coral Bay Area of Particular Concern Report, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 1171)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Cruz Bay, Enighed Pond Area of Particular Concern Report, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 1172)
  - #125, Area of Particular Concern (APC) Management Plans, Christiansted Waterfront Report, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 1173)